<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AquaStep</string>
    <string name="devices">Bluetooth Devices</string>
    <string name="about_us_title">About us</string>
    <string name="about_us_text">At AquaStep, we are dedicated to promoting a healthy lifestyle through optimal hydration.\nOur app helps you track and improve your water intake, making hydration convenient and personalized.</string>
    <string name="about_the_app_title">About the App</string>
    <string name="about_the_app_text">
       AquaStep is an innovative app that calculates your ideal water intake based on your activity level, body weight, and environment.
        Stay on top of your hydration goals and maintain a healthy water balance effortlessly.
    </string>
    <string name="instructions_title">Instructions</string>
    <string name="instructions_text">1. Place the Sensor: Attach our sensor to your belt. Make sure it\'s located on your strong leg.\n2. Connect to the AquaStep bluetooth device called "AquaStepBT"\n3. "Go to Sleep" Button: Press the button to End the daily tracking. The app will then reset and start tracking the next day.</string>
    <string-array name="random_strings">
        <item>Drinking enough water can help improve cognitive function and concentration.</item>
        <item>Drinking water can help boost your metabolism and aid in weight loss.</item>
        <item>Water is essential for the transportation of nutrients and oxygen throughout the body.</item>
        <item>Staying hydrated can help prevent muscle cramps and improve athletic performance.</item>
        <item>Drinking water before a meal can help reduce calorie intake and promote healthy digestion.</item>
        <item>Water helps regulate body temperature and prevents overheating.</item>
        <item>Dehydration can contribute to headaches and migraines.</item>
        <item>Water is crucial for flushing out waste and toxins from the body.</item>
        <item>Staying properly hydrated can help prevent kidney stones.</item>
        <item>Water is necessary to produce saliva, which aids in digestion.</item>
        <item>Water plays a vital role in joint lubrication and can help prevent joint pain.</item>
        <item>Adequate water intake can help reduce the risk of urinary tract infections.</item>
        <item>Water is essential for the proper functioning of the cardiovascular system.</item>
        <item>Drinking water can help prevent hangovers by flushing out alcohol from the system.</item>
        <item>Water is the best choice for hydration, as sugary drinks can contribute to weight gain and tooth decay.</item>
        <item>Staying hydrated can help alleviate fatigue and improve energy levels.</item>
        <item>Water is crucial for maintaining the balance of body fluids.</item>
        <item>Drinking enough water can help reduce the risk of certain types of cancer, such as bladder and colon cancer.</item>
        <item>Water is vital for the health and proper functioning of the liver.</item>
        <item>Staying hydrated can help prevent the formation of painful kidney stones.</item>
        <item>Water can help relieve heartburn and acid reflux symptoms.</item>
        <item>Drinking water can help prevent and alleviate the symptoms of urinary incontinence.</item>
        <item>Water is necessary to produce breast milk in nursing mothers.</item>
        <item>Drinking water can help reduce the risk of developing chronic illnesses, such as diabetes and hypertension.</item>
        <item>Water is crucial for the lubrication and cushioning of the spinal cord and other sensitive tissues.</item>
        <item>Staying properly hydrated can help improve mood and reduce stress levels.</item>
        <item>Water is essential for the maintenance of overall good health and well-being.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="cancel">I drank 1 cup</string>

</resources>